A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 1903-1947
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series II. Files, 1903-1947
  - Dr. A.W. Drinkard, Jr., Director, correspondence files, 1938-1939
    - Jones, E.B., Treasurer of VA, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 64)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 65)
    - Koiner, Hon. Ged W., Commissioner of Agriculture & Immigration, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 66)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 67)
    - Labor, U.S. Bureau of, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 68)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 69)
    - Magill, E.C., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 70)
    - Mailing Lists, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 71)
    - Marshall, H.C., Charlotte Court House, Va, 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 72)
    - Matthews, E.M., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 73)
    - Maxton, J.L., 1938-1939 (Box 115, Folder 74)
    - Meek, J.H., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Michael, R.D., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Miller, E.C., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Mooers, Prof. C.A., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Moore, H.L., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Moore, R.C., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Mc Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - McNeil, R.H., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Newell, Dr. Wilmon, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Obenshain, S.S., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - P Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Perkins, W.R., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Pinckard, J.A., Jr., Chatham, Va, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Potter, P.B., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Pratt, A.D., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Price, Dean H.L., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Programs, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Richmond Times-Dispatch, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Sanders, Prof. Harry W., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Satorius, Mary, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Saunders, W.D., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Schoene, W.J., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - Shear, G.M., 1938 (Box 116, Folder 28)
    - Shulkcum, Edward (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - Sjogren, J.W., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 30)
    - Smith, A.G., 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 31)
    - Soil Conservation Committee, State, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 32)
    - Soil Conservation Service, U.S.D.A. (Box 116, Folder 33)
    - Southern Planter, The (Box 116, Folder 34)
    - State Land-Use Committee, John R. Hutcheson, Chair (Box 116, Folder 35)
    - Stiles, Dr. W.C., 1939 (Box 116, Folder 36)
    - Strong, W.O., 1939 (Box 116, Folder 37)
    - Stuckey, Director H.R., 1939 (Box 116, Folder 38)
    - Superintendent of Documents, 1939 (Box 116, Folder 39)
    - T Miscellaneous, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 40)
    - Tate, Dr. Mildred T. (Box 116, Folder 41)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 42)
    - TVA Staff Correspondence, 1939 (Box 116, Folder 43)
    - Wild Life Service, VA Cooperative, Monthly Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 116, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 116, Folder 45)
  - Addy, C.E., 1940-1941 (Box 116, Folder 46)
  - Applications, 1940-1941 (Box 116, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 116, Folder 48)
  - Wild Life, 1942-1943 (Box 116, Folder 49)
  - Bait Traps-E.L. Wood, 1939 (Box 116, Folder 50)
  - Infested Tags, 1940 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 117, Folder 2, 19)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1929-1931 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1927-1929 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1925-1927 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1923-1925 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1913-1914, 1916, 1918 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1910, 1912-1913 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1908-1909 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1907 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1902, 1906 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1930, 1937-1939 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 117, Folder 13-14, 20-23)
  - Digestion Experiments (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Time Book (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Plantings (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Triangle Buckwheat Experiments (Box 117, Folder 18)